this tutorial is about automatic bull
本教程是关于自动牛市的
剥离的原理是，你有一个
this tutorial is about automatic bull
strips the principle is that you have a
卡条，它粘在一侧
当页面打开时，该条跨过
strips the principle is that you have a
strip of card and it's stuck to one side
另一页上下翻页
当页面打开时，它将拉动该条
strip of card and it's stuck to one side
as the page opens this strip goes across
因此，这一前进的方向可以是
用来使其弯曲成弓形
as the page opens this strip goes across
the other page under and out again and
抬起皮瓣抬起平行四边形
你知道它具有所有这些用途，所以我会
the other page under and out again and
as the page opens it pulls that strip
给你看其他例子
这是一个正在鞠躬的人
as the page opens it pulls that strip
and so this end that's moving can be
形状，在这种情况下，
那就是把它拉到下面
and so this end that's moving can be
used to make it raise up a bowing shape
你下台的边缘，它走了
通过那里下面的一个插槽，但是
used to make it raise up a bowing shape
raise up a flap raise up a parallelogram
实际上并没有进入哪个页面
意味着这边这边可能会趋向
raise up a flap raise up a parallelogram
you know it has all these uses so I'll
举起一点，但在这个例子中
它实际上表现得很好
you know it has all these uses so I'll
show you examples of these other ones so
另一个例子是如果
你这样看就可以看
show you examples of these other ones so
here's one this is raising up a bow in
确实进入页面下方并出来
再次，这提起这瓣
here's one this is raising up a bow in
shape and in this case that the strip
然后举起平行四边形，然后
在这个例子中，这就是拉
shape and in this case that the strip
that's pulling it just goes underneath
带拉起这种弓形和
因为它是弯曲的形状
that's pulling it just goes underneath
this edge you step down and it goes
将笔直的卡片粘贴到
曲线上的不同点
this edge you step down and it goes
through a slot underneath there but it
都会以不同的角度抬起
我再给你看一个例子
through a slot underneath there but it
doesn't actually go under the page which
最简单的机制
这是David Pellom和
doesn't actually go under the page which
means this end this side here can tend
当你打开这个
它拉动了假价格，所以现在我们
means this end this side here can tend
to lift up a bit but in this example
只是使最简单的一种，所以你会
需要像这样的基础表
to lift up a bit but in this example
it's actually behaving pretty well this
将它折成两半
完全正确，不要再张纸
it's actually behaving pretty well this
is another example here's the strip if
卡，然后将其切成两半
纵向画几张
is another example here's the strip if
you look at it this way you can see it
准则使用标尺绘制
几个平行的引导线沿着
you look at it this way you can see it
does go under the page and come out
它的长度将标尺放在中间
对于两个准则
does go under the page and come out
again and that lifts this flap which
现在将标签页夹到一端，这是一个
粘贴标签，所以大约半英寸
again and that lifts this flap which
then lifts this parallelogram and then
宽或一厘米的折叠
另一端剪掉大约一英寸
then lifts this parallelogram and then
in this example here is this is the pull
两个半厘米的东西
像那样稍微缩短一点
in this example here is this is the pull
strip pulling up this bowing shape and
并在其上折叠粘合标签
就像现在把你的基础表放一个
strip pulling up this bowing shape and
because it's a curved shape you can
对折起名字，就像
这是中央沟
because it's a curved shape you can
stick straight pieces of card onto it at
基本表，然后将其折叠，因此
就在卡的外边缘内
stick straight pieces of card onto it at
different points on the curve and they
这样当东西平的时候
它不只是现在不在
different points on the curve and they
will all lift up at different angles so
长边这是条带去的地方
要在这个长边上画一个
will all lift up at different angles so
I'll just show you one more example of
小指南再次在这里
一厘米可以帮助整个
I'll just show you one more example of
the mechanism this is the most simple
坚持不动，东西移动会更顺畅
在一起
the mechanism this is the most simple
this is worms wiggle by David Pellom and
现在拿一把工艺刀或剪刀，
剪掉地带
this is worms wiggle by David Pellom and
as you open this
这些指南内的毫米数
行，以便您正在制作的条带是
as you open this
it pulls the fake price across so now we
只是会比
您绘制的指导线，然后
it pulls the fake price across so now we
just make the simplest kind so you'll
沿着第二个第二指南
现在另一端拿出一个
just make the simplest kind so you'll
need a base sheet something like this
介于两个准则之间
这一个你开始只吃一顿饭
need a base sheet something like this
fold it in half crease it really
或折线上方1毫米，
带到外面一毫米或两毫米
fold it in half crease it really
thoroughly right no take another sheet
准则，因此您的范围更广
现在，您可以调整一下缝隙
thoroughly right no take another sheet
of card and just cut it in half
所有这些粘贴选项卡
弯道好了，现在将其折叠
of card and just cut it in half
lengthways so draw a couple of
这是你的那条折痕
仅此折叠结束，并确保
lengthways so draw a couple of
guidelines use your ruler to draw a
拉条紧贴的
在这两个之间，当你拉
guidelines use your ruler to draw a
couple of parallel guide lines down the
这一切都只是容易移动
条带之间有一些间隙
couple of parallel guide lines down the
length of it put the ruler in the middle
这两个选项卡激活将其放置在
的地方，所以你有最尖端的
for the two guidelines
拉条的中央
现在这两个标签在沟渠下折叠
now folder a tab on to one end this is a
你把胶水粘在它们上
同时，他们将成为
now folder a tab on to one end this is a
gluing tab so it's about half an inch
像这样折叠在下面
他们都是这个机制的所有标签
gluing tab so it's about half an inch
wide or one centimeter fold that really
承受很大的压力，所以请确保
胶水直达折痕
wide or one centimeter fold that really
well the other end cut off about an inch
而且你知道那里很好
粘在下面
well the other end cut off about an inch
two and a half centimeters something
拉带紧贴脊柱
按下它就可以了
two and a half centimeters something
like that just make it slightly shorter
它正在工作，您现在就可以
只需拉一下并确保它是
like that just make it slightly shorter
and fold a gluing tab on to that as well
举起好吧，所以举起所有
现在，您将胶水平放在标签上
like now take your base sheet put one
您将胶水放在标签的顶部
标签确实需要很大的压力，所以
like now take your base sheet put one
name against the crease so it's like
确保这是很好的胶合
现在您可以关闭底座了
name against the crease so it's like
this here's the central gully of the
会发现其自然黏附
位置给胶水片刻
this here's the central gully of the
base sheet and now fold it over so it's
去然后打开它，所以有
你鞠躬的事，然后是的，如果你
base sheet and now fold it over so it's
just within the outer edge of the card
希望您可以将碎片粘贴到此
所以你可以看到不同的角度
so that when the when the thing is flat
根据你坚持的地方举起来
他们，你可以坚持他们
so that when the when the thing is flat
it doesn't doesn't just out now on the
但如果你坚持下去
这样的一面，他们
it doesn't doesn't just out now on the
long side this is where the strips going
更可能扑向基地
当它关闭时，最简单的方法是
long side this is where the strips going
to be on this long side just draw a
让他们这样走，你
这些只需要一点胶水
to be on this long side just draw a
little guideline here again it's about
根本不用承受任何压力，所以有
一棒一顶
little guideline here again it's about
one centimeter in this helps the whole
坚持一个完全不同的角度
你可以坚持一半，这样你就可以
one centimeter in this helps the whole
thing move more smoothly when you stick
看到那是你真正看到的
飞机，然后如您所见，我已经完成了
thing move more smoothly when you stick
it together
这个粗糙的地方有点低，所以他们出去了
你在这里也有沟壑，所以你可以
it together
now take a craft knife or scissors and
您可以在今天粘贴其他弹出式窗口，以便
在这里，我们有帮助动物的
now take a craft knife or scissors and
cut out the strip just a couple of
罗伯茨·奥布达（Robertsóbuda）和
他玩过的第一个
cut out the strip just a couple of
millimeters on the inside of these guide
将零件粘在上面的想法
圆角的形状使这些鳞片
millimeters on the inside of these guide
lines so that the strip you're making is
当它关闭时，打开并关闭那些
所有下一个都以不同的角度抬起
lines so that the strip you're making is
just going to be slightly narrower than
一个是一分钱的飞行器
这是价差，所以这是
just going to be slightly narrower than
the guide lines you've drawn and then
曲线形状这是它粘贴的条
在这边向下穿过
the guide lines you've drawn and then
cut along that second second guide
脊柱潜入页面下方，然后
会在下面再次出现
right now the other ends take out a
气球并附着在
气球，以便页面打开
right now the other ends take out a
piece in between the two guidelines and
气球上升，所以如果我们看这个
您可能会在这里看到的方式
piece in between the two guidelines and
this one you start just a couple of meal
您
电视带在下面
this one you start just a couple of meal
or a millimeter above the fold line and
气球，还有另一个例子
在我会仔细阅读这本书，
or a millimeter above the fold line and
take it to a millimeter or two outside
他们看一看，所以这是一个
我们只是看着不是这个
take it to a millimeter or two outside
the guidelines so you're getting a wider
所以这是这里的这些是
这两个这是地带
the guidelines so you're getting a wider
gap here and now you can can just trim
它附在页面的这一侧
穿过脊椎下面
gap here and now you can can just trim
all these gluing tabs just take those
马上就出现了
在协和飞机的机翼下面
all these gluing tabs just take those
corners off okay now just fold it over
拉起皮瓣，然后调和
建立在平行四边形上，这样
corners off okay now just fold it over
this is your piece with a crease there
一个条附在这里
页面的一侧，然后跨过
this is your piece with a crease there
just this fold is over and make sure
脊椎，走到下面，然后在这里
您可以看到它抬起并且正在抬起
just this fold is over and make sure
that the that the pull strip fits snugly
皮瓣然后提起
如果我这样支撑平行四边形
that the that the pull strip fits snugly
between these two so when when you pull
你可以看到平行四边形
把它和直升机向东抬起
between these two so when when you pull
it it all just moves moves easily
在平行四边形的顶部，这是
下一个是绿野仙踪
it it all just moves moves easily
there's some clearance between the strip
这里有几个例子
这是一个多重剥离
there's some clearance between the strip
and these two tabs activation lay it in
拉这个，这是先生。跳闸
停留在这一边
and these two tabs activation lay it in
place so you've got the very tip of the
在页面背面下方
有一系列的拉条
place so you've got the very tip of the
of the pull strip up against the central
他们都通过页面出现
然后把这些罂粟花举起来，你
of the pull strip up against the central
gully now these two tabs fold underneath
可以看到这只鸟的翅膀在这里
从页面出现的条带
gully now these two tabs fold underneath
you put glue on them both glue them at
页面打开，您会看到该条
消失在页面拉下
you put glue on them both glue them at
the same time so they're going to be
向上飞过鸟的翅膀
在这里，我们是弯曲的形状
the same time so they're going to be
folded underneath like that put glue on
儿子
地带在这里后面隐藏
folded underneath like that put glue on
them both all the tabs on this mechanism
在这只飞猴或任何它后面
它被卡在这边吗
them both all the tabs on this mechanism
take quite a lot of stress so make sure
页面下方的脊柱，然后
抬头仰望你会看到的塔内
take quite a lot of stress so make sure
the glue goes right up to the creases
这里有带
出现并在这一方面拉动
the glue goes right up to the creases
and you know that there they are well
把它拉成弯曲的形状
然后我们有小红帽
and you know that there they are well
glued put it underneath put the tip of
布鲁斯·福斯特（Bruce Foster）创作的
狼头是你的拉带动作
glued put it underneath put the tip of
the pull strip up against the spine
打开皮瓣，你可以看到这里的
剥开它把狼的头翻过来，
press it down okay and you can just test
条带连接到此襟翼
它附在爆炸后面
press it down okay and you can just test
that it's working you can now you can
在页面下再次出现
襟翼打开，它变成了狼头
that it's working you can now you can
just pull this and make sure that it is
然后最后一个是
这本书的结尾是最后一页
just pull this and make sure that it is
lifting up okay so that's lifting up all
这条被附在这边
它藏在它走的猫下
lifting up okay so that's lifting up all
right now you put glue with the tab flat
通过中的孔
弯曲的形状碰到附着
right now you put glue with the tab flat
you put glue on the top of the tab this
整理并将其拉起，然后他们
所有这些东西都被利用了
you put glue on the top of the tab this
tab really takes a lot of stress so make
曲线的
以不同的角度提起它
tab really takes a lot of stress so make
sure this is very very well glued
下本书是前一天晚上
圣诞节罗伯特佛和
sure this is very very well glued
and now you can close the base so it's
最后，你已经有了这个
如果这是一个壮观的冬季场景
and now you can close the base so it's
going to find its natural sticking
这是V型起重架
但这是这两个房子
going to find its natural sticking
position give it a moment for the glue
由自动拉带提起
他们实际上在桥下
position give it a moment for the glue
to go off and then open it up so there's
就像你看到的那样
他们都关闭了，但是
to go off and then open it up so there's
your bowing thing and then yeah if you
打开拉条，您可以看到
他们在桥下
your bowing thing and then yeah if you
want you can stick pieces onto onto this
页面隐藏的拉条，除了一个是
附着在这边下面
want you can stick pieces onto onto this
so you can see the different angles that
拉起这所房子，这一个
带连接到这边去
so you can see the different angles that
lift up according to where you stick
在下面拉起这个端壁
然后升起平行四边形
lift up according to where you stick
them and you can stick them on either
使整个房子成型
最后是大卫的蓝色2
them and you can stick them on either
side of this but if you stick them on
卡特，这有一个完整的系列
他们打开的顶部形状处理
side of this but if you stick them on
this side coming up this way they're
在第18课中有，仅此而已
地带真的很明显
this side coming up this way they're
more likely to bashing to the base as it
在这里，您可以看到它们从
以这种方式查看您周围的页面
more likely to bashing to the base as it
as it closes so the easiest one is to
可以看到它如何附在这边
在这边下面出现
as it closes so the easiest one is to
have them coming up this way and you
再次拉起这个开放的顶部
形状，所以这只是一个整体
have them coming up this way and you
just need a little bit of glue these
阵列和四个拉条，您可以
只是很清楚地看到他们都是
just need a little bit of glue these
don't take any stress at all so there's
工作，如果你看看它是否结束
你可以看到全部
don't take any stress at all so there's
one stick one on the on the top I'll
他们都那样移动
拉这些拉这些锥体
one stick one on the on the top I'll
stick it a completely different angle
进入直道，就这样拉
保罗带被覆盖在这个
stick it a completely different angle
you can stick one halfway up so you can
我的书弹出设计和纸张
机械师
you can stick one halfway up so you can
see that's something you can really see
您
the plane then as you see I've done a